#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/pratik-mishra-661005166 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Algorithms

Machine Learning

Competitive Programming

### Certifications

Python and Django Full Stack Web Developer BootCamp

Learn Machine learning by building Projects

Machine Learning A-Z.

### **Publications**

RandomForestClassifier
vs IsolationForest and
LocalOutlierFactor for Credit Card
Fraud Detection

# Pratik Mishra

GSoC Student '20 @CHAOSS Kolkata

## Summary

Google Summer of Code 2020 @CHAOSS.

Former Research Consultant, WorldQuant,LLC.

Machine Learning Enthusiast and Full Stack Web Developer with Python and Django and SQL.

Competitive Programmer - Ranked 189 in CodeChef October Long challenge(Division-2)

Computer languages-C++, Python 3.

## Experience

Google Summer of Code GSoC Student '20 @CHAOSS May 2020 - Present (4 months)

WorldQuant
Research Consultant
December 2018 - October 2019 (11 months)

Mumbai, India

Simulated around 5000 alphas and developed 700+ submittable alphas( algorithms for trading).

Achieved Gold level in Worldquant Alpha Challenge and awarded a position of Research Consultant.

### Education

Calcutta University, Kolkata

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2018 - 2022)

ALLEN CAREER INSTITUTE ,KOTA

PCM · (2016 - 2018)